[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[The D Dorm]
What was it you said?
Do not tell me you have found a way
to prove that Grandpa
is real...
have you?
We had better prove that he is not crazy.
He isn't crazy, Grandpa.
He dressed like this because
he's going to audition for 'Bang Rachan vs Predator.'
You are talking to yourself again.
Does that mean you are communicating with Grandpa?
He's not around here, but he is here.
There.
He's right there.
- Grandpa. - Hm?
He doesn't believe me.
Alright, then. Let's do what we planned.
I am not going to do that.
Come on, Grandpa!
If you don't do this,
no one will help you find Grandma Gaysorn's relatives.
Your method is horrendous!
How is it horrendous, Grandpa?!
Hey, think of it like this.
For you to meet Grandma Gaysorn,
your first love,
the person you failed to keep your promise to,
and the person you wish to apologize to the most,
you have to do this
in order to reincarnate.
Wait!
What is it that you are going to have your grandpa do?
Enlighten me.
Can you stop with that Early Modern English thing?
It's always late.
Grandpa,
do it.
Has he lost his mind?
Whoa!
It is super white.
Is he wearing white underwear?
He is not wearing underwear.
His left cheek is super white.
Dax, you're not wearing underwear, huh?!
Hey!
How did you know I'm not wearing any?
Oh, I know.
I'm dressed in an old-fashioned style.
So that's why
you could guess, huh?
You still don't believe me?
Grandpa.
Huh?
He doesn't believe me.
You'll have to look closer than that.
Do I really have to shove my face in his butt to prove myself?
Come on, Grandpa.
So?
His butt has a bruise.
It looks like...bite marks.
- Dax! - Huh?
Does your butt
have a bruise
that looks like bite marks?
Hey!
- What... - Am I right?!
Yeah, I have it.
Cause I just auditioned for a role in 'Ghost, Don't Bite My Butt.'
The mark is still here. It still hurts.
So you still don't believe me?
Grandpa, this will be the last one.
- Shove your face right into the front. - Hey, hey, hey!
Don't!
Fine, I believe you.
The reason I asked you for help
is because I don't have anyone else.
I want you to be my sidekick
and help me find Grandma Gaysorn.
Mm...
Just think of it as helping an old man.
What do I have to do?
Before Grandpa passed away,
someone dropped Grandma Gaysorn's photo on the stairs.
We have to check the cameras
to see if the person who dropped it
is a relative of Grandma Gaysorn or not.
- Maybe they are. - Hello, how can I help you?
Shoot!
What's your friend wearing?!
Oh, he's auditioning for a role.
Never mind him.
I want to see the security camera footage
from the day my grandpa passed away.
You saw it with the police already, didn't you?
Why do you wanna see it again?
Are you plotting some kind of evil plan to sell this dorm again?
- Whoa... - Hey,
it's not that.
You're too biased.
- I want to show it to Dax. - Yes.
Cause he's auditioning as a soldier
who had a heart attack after hearing the bomb and passed away.
So he knows what it was like when Grandpa had a heart attack.
- Huh? - Huh?
From what I've seen in dramas,
they clutch their chest
before slowly falling to their death.
"I'll wait for you at the Milky Way!"
Like that.
Hey, don't lump me in with those amateur actors.
Pain has many forms of expression.
Like getting shot to death.
It depends on the country.
In Thai movies!
Bang!
Just...
you...
wait!
Like that.
- Indian movies! - Bang!
- Dhadang, dhadang, ding-ding-ding. - Oh...
- Ding-ding-ding-ding. - Gotta have a tune before you die.
- Bollywood. - Bollywood.
Korean movies!
Bang!
The song? Where's the song?
- ♫You...♫ - ♫You...♫
♫You are my destiny♫
I...
You what?
love...you.
Something like that.
Awesome, that was great, Dax.
You can't see
the camera footage, no matter what!
Huh?!
I'm the owner of this dorm, so why can't I see it?!
I said you can't watch it!
Ugh!
You can't see it
because the hard disk is broken!
I'm going to get it fixed.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine, but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains, remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]
I think
if we can't see the camera footage,
we'll have to find Grandma Gaysorn's photo.
So we can make a missing-person poster for her.
Why don't you ask your grandpa
how he was holding the photo when he passed away?
Huh?
If he was holding it like this...
Mm.
When he passed,
it'd be like this.
And?
The photo wouldn't fall far.
- I see. - Yes.
- But if he was holding it like this, - Mm.
like a ninja star, when he passed,
he'd fall like this.
The photo could be anywhere.
I see...
Hey,
can I really rely on you two?
Let's just look for Grandma Gaysorn's photo.
Look around here.
- Right. - Let's try.
Hey, I found it!
Huh?!
You did?!
Is this Grandma Gaysorn's photo?
Yes, I remember her photo!
Oh, thank the heavens.
Gaysorn, we are going to meet soon!
She's dripping!
Right?
In the past,
everyone who met her
said she was dripping with beauty.
The paint is dripping!
The photo is all messed up!
What?
Can I see?
- Look. - Whoa.
- What do we do? - Oh...
Oh no!
I can't see her face at all, Grandpa.
What are they doing here in secret?
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
You only got my low angle. Can you switch things up a bit?
Wait a sec. I'm planking.
I can feel my abs burning.
Ugh, I knew it.
You're wearing a new outfit again.
Is that my curtain or my blanket?
No, Mom,
I bought this myself.
- Isn't this cool? - Yes.
Hey, Mom.
I just posted this on Instagram,
and everyone complimented me.
Oh, so cool.
Take care. I don't want anything
to happen to you, except becoming my boyfriend.
So, so, so, so cute.
I want to keep that smile all to myself.
Dolly.
- Hm? - Do it.
Like, post more photos?
- Do some planks. - What?
- Huh?! - Go!
Right now?!
Right now.
I haven't changed yet.
- No need to. Any outfit is fine. - Hey...
- Go. - Ugh...
Get down.
Lift yourself up.
- Mom. - Yeah?
I don't want any fat, meat, or carbs
in this evening's salad.
Only greens and beans.
You're picky as if you were a sacred ox.
Before you eat health-y,
why don't you help-me first?
Okay.
Oh,
isn't Dawin here yet?
Right, Mom?
I'm here.
Whoa.
What happened to you?
You can tell me.
I was shuffling the cards a bit too much,
so my fingers got stuck like this. See?
You were punched because your fingers got stuck?
My customer thought I was flirting with their partner.
- Oh... - Ugh!
Bad luck after bad luck. You really have the worst luck, huh?
The other day, he fell into a drain.
Yesterday, a motorbike almost hit him.
Get ordained for a few months. Maybe things will get better.
I'm used to it.
It's been like this my entire life.
By the way...
what would you like me to tell you about your fortune?
I want to know if the coffee shop owner downstairs
is a good match for me.
His shop is about to open, but I've never even seen him.
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
[DO-MUN-DRIP]
Whoa...
All swords, huh?
That means
your fortunes and his
stab each other.
You two are a terrible match.
Oh no.
We live so close.
What should I do?
Pick one more card, Auntie Duang.
This one.
It says
you'll face karma
that can't be avoided.
You'll keep running into someone you hate!
Huh?
You have a person you hate?
All I see is people who hate you,
cause you love gossiping about others.
Wow,
Mr. Community Relations Officer,
you're kind to others,
but mean to your mother?
True.
But wait,
the card says
this kind of person will live aimlessly,
with no clear goal.
Just living happily day by day.
Does this sound familiar, Mom?
That sounds like Dad.
Your dad?
He's been gone for more than twenty years.
He's not coming back.
The card says you'll get to meet him
really soon.
Hey, Mom!
I'll get to meet him, right?
Mom, he's really coming back, right?
No way.
He's already dead.
How do you know he's already dead?
Dad just went to the market,
and then he just disappeared.
Maybe...
he just got lost.
For twenty years?
Mm.
Did he go to Mars or something?
Hey, seriously,
are you still hoping he'll come back?
Because to me, he's long gone.
No!
Dead!
Boys...
Ugh, what's wrong with you guys?
Every time their dad is mentioned, they act like this.
The security cameras are broken.
Grandma's photo is no good.
Alright,
let's knock on every door in this dorm,
so we'll know who is Grandma Gaysorn's relative.
Hello, I'm the new owner of this dorm...
Take out the trash for me.
Hello!
- Oh! - Whoa, whoa!
Oh, Dobby...
Hello, I'm the new owner. Grandpa's grandson.
Well, I...
- Hello. - Hello.
Hey!
- Don't close the door yet! - Whoa!
Dobby, Dobby, Dobby!
Dobby!
Dobby. Dobby!
- Hello. - Oh, hello.
Khaidao.
A Rottweiler...
Oh, don't worry. He's friendly.
- It's baring its teeth, though! - Khaidao, dear.
Well, he's smiling.
- Smiling? - He's actually friendly.
I can even let go of the leash.
- Friendly? - Huh?
Don't let go!
Whoa. Khaidao! Khaidao! Khaidao!
Khaidao! Those!
- Those balls aren't dog toys! - Khaidao!
How are you feeling, Dobby?
Ouch, my balls!
Ow...
- Ow, it stings. - Sorry, sorry.
I have fought many battles,
yet never have I seen a comrade
bitten in the balls like this.
Well, there's me!
Come on...
What are you laughing at, Grandpa?
I'm like this because of you!
Ouch!
Oh, it stings.
Hey, Dobby,
don't you think that's a bit weird?
Why do the people in this dorm
hate you so much?
- Right? - Yeah.
I already said that
I won't sell this dorm.
That's right.
Maybe it is because of me.
Back when I was still alive...
When they saw the photo they were looking for was ruined,
they went around knocking on our tenants' doors.
I happened to hear that...
Yes?
Your hair smells good.
Want to smell something else, then?
I'm sorry, I got carried away.
Well...
they were pretty far away, so I couldn't hear them.
Maybe
he went around introducing himself as the new owner.
Building a good relationship with his tenants!
Mr. Dobby, how nice of you.
No way.
Someone as ungrateful as him?
You really think he'd think of others?
Can't be.
Then, how about this?
If you want to know their plans, it's very simple.
We can invite them to a party,
get them drunk, then ask them.
Whoa...
That's a good plan, Dum.
Despicable!
That's my little brother.
Well done.
I don't know if I should be proud…
Hey!
So, the reason everyone in this dorm hates you
is because your grandpa
told them that
you and your mother abandoned him?!
Exactly!
Just think about it.
Grandpa went around badmouthing my mother,
saying that whenever he came to visit,
she'd drive him away like a dog.
When in reality,
Grandpa never even bothered with her.
He never came to see her or his own grandson!
Let that sit with you.
Why, though?
I was lonely.
I wanted some attention,
so I made up some stories.
- Stories? Stories, my foot... - Hey, hey!
Ouch, it hurts!
Dax!
Hey, sorry, sorry.
But can you stop fighting?
Alright, I'll stop.
We have to think about what we're going to do next.
The cameras are broken.
Grandma Gaysorn's photo is no good.
Everyone in this dorm hates you, too.
What should we do now?
There is a way.
Hm?
You know full well
that the tenants
love Danis.
Just get Danis on your side.
Everything will be easier.
As if it were that easy, Grandpa!
You have to picture this.
Danis hates my guts.
Very much.
Why would she help me?!
Come on!
Huh?!
You're hosting a welcome party for me?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Of course!
It's not your concern.
Just get to the point.
Well...I feel bad for what I did this morning.
I judged you too harshly.
We have to take care of the dorm together,
so I wanted to get to know you better. Yeah?
Um, alright.
Then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Is your mustache crooked?
Mm.
Your mustache, not your eyebrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Go check.
Don't forget.
See you tomorrow.
Dobby.
Huh?
I think something is off.
She was just yelling at us this morning.
But now she's hosting a party for us?
It does seem off.
But we don't have a choice, do we?
We have to risk it.
You're right...
If you want a puppy,
you'll have to venture into a dog's den.
Was it not "a tiger's den"?
Well, she bites back like a dog.
I see.
So it should be a dog, Grandpa.
[The D Dorm]
[Duangjai's Kitchen, Made-to-Order Food]
Hello, Mom.
Oh, wow...
Today,
I'm doing fittings for the actors from one31.
I'll get to meet Bie today.
Would you like his autograph?
I don't want his autograph.
I want his leg hair.
He was at the temple for so long,
I bet his leg hair is definitely sacred.
Okay, Mom.
I'll get going.
Mm.
See you.
- Okay. - Wait, Dolly.
If you want to stay safe…
why don't you let the cards guide you?
- A truck could flatten you as you walk. - Hey...
Trust me,
you never know when bad luck will strike.
Ow!
What's this, Auntie?!
Oh! Venerable Salty Grandpa's phallic amulet.
Sadhu. Oh dear.
Pass it here.
Oh, I thought I'd lost it. Gosh.
Found it. Sadhu.
Mom!
- Oh... - Oh, dear.
Sadhu, sadhu.
I think you should let the cards guide you.
How can you be
this unlucky every day?
Mom,
why are the dogs barking?
They're barking at your brother.
- Hey! - Whoa!
Um...you're a cop.
What's this costume?
Today, the community relations officers
have an activity to promote waste sorting.
Oh...my brother.
What are you laughing at?
We still have to talk about yesterday.
Who'd want to talk to someone so narrow-minded?
You can't even forgive
your own father.
Stop defending that selfish man!
How did you know Dad was selfish?!
You were only four then.
Probably couldn't even wipe your own butt.
You were still in Mom's womb, squishing her large intestine.
What would you know?
All you did was lie there talking to Mom's poop!
Hey, boys,
don't talk about food while someone is eating poop.
- Oops. - Oh.
Eating food. Sorry.
Dolly, you should go to work.
- Mom, look at him. - Go to work.
Sadhu,
I hope the cards Dawin read
mean Dad is coming back.
I want to see someone die of frustration.
- Where the hell are you going?! - Dollar, Dollar.
Go get changed.
Can you also go buy a wealth-beckoning goddess with me?
I want to give it to the coffee shop owner downstairs.
But didn't Dawin's cards
say that you aren't compatible with him?
Dollar,
we're neighboring shops.
It's good to be kind.
Our fortunes could change.
They couldn't, Auntie.
The cards clearly said
your luck
will stab, stab, stab the other person!
Oh...
Go get changed. Hurry.
Still staring? Are you gonna buy it or not?
What's it gonna be?
Whoa,
that face card pierced through the smoke.
[Drip, occupation: coffee shop owner]
The grilled chicken smells good,
but...the smoke is burning my eyes.
Then why are you still standing here?
So, just one skewer?
Yes.
Twenty baht.
No QR payments.
No transfers.
No large bills.
Yes.
Aw,
cool but starving, huh?
Auntie Aoy.
Yes?
I'll pay for him.
Huh?
It's okay.
It's on me.
Thank you.
What's going on?
What?
Hey!
Wait!
Middle-class people are so kind.
Gosh!
Your chicken tastes even better than Gordon's.
What Don?
If you mean Don Chedi, of course it's better.
I used Bang Tan's recipe.
You're amazing, Auntie.
Cheers!
Let me join in, too.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
Oh...
Are you trying to speedrun drinking?
Everyone else drinks from glasses,
but you drink from a vase. You really wanna drink, huh?
Hey!
There goes our drink, ugh...
Back in my day, there were no glasses.
If I don't drink from a vase,
what should I drink from?
Hey,
why are you drinking water?
Let's indulge in some liquor.
Come on!
Don't!
You call this indulging in liquor? You're pouring it over my head!
You go drink with them, yeah?
Well, I... I can't indulge in liquor.
I'm allergic.
You can have Dennis do whatever you want,
but do not let her drink.
Try talking to her about a badminton court.
She has wanted it for a long time now.
If you say it,
you might win her over,
and maybe she will work with you.
Um, hey...
Hm?
Do you see the free space over there?
There.
Mm,
I do.
Well, I don't.
What?
But you asked me.
Hey...do not joke around.
Just kidding. Maybe I'm drinking too much.
I see.
Hey, look there.
I just think that
if we leave it like that,
the area will go to waste.
But we can build a badminton court
so the tenants
can exercise down there.
What do you think?
Hey!
You want to build a badminton court, too?
I had the same idea!
- See? See? - Wow!
Oh, oh.
You see, we're here
to party today, right?
Let's not talk business yet, yeah?
I think...
we should get to know each other better.
Sounds good?
I like your idea.
Right?!
Exactly.
They say people grow closer
when they drink together a lot.
- Yes. - Don't stop drinking.
- Cheers! - True!
- Cheers! - Yes, cheers!
Me, too.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Cheers!
Well, they are close.
Close to sleeping like a log.
I think...
what happens next might not be very fun.
I cannot stay here anymore.
I should leave.
Water...
Whoa!
Come closer. I'm gonna whisper.
Whisper in my ear.
- Now's the time. - Mm.
They're drunk.
You can ask them what you wanna know. Go on.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
Mr. Dobby.
Mr. Dobby!
Mr. Dobby...
- Whoa! - Whoa!
It's nothing, Mr. Dobby!
Why did you knock on the tenants' door?
What were you talking about?
Hm?
Oh...
I was...
What were you talking about?
Go make me another drink!
Man, I'm feeling so good right now...
Go make me another one!
Maybe he hasn't hit his limit yet,
but don't worry.
Mm.
I'll make him a drink.
I'll make it strong.
When he's wasted,
- you can ask him again, alright? - Right.
Mm, okay.
- Leave it to me. Don't worry. - Okay, okay.
Let me make you a drink.
Mr. Dobby, he will make it for you.
Hey...why are there so many glasses?
- It's right here. - Oh.
Okay.
- Can you do it? - Ah, easy.
Hey, hey, hey, are you good?
Alcohol is weird.
I drink through my mouth, but my legs stop working.
I only have two legs, how are they tangled?
- Hey! - Whoa!
That's enough, my beloved brother.
He hasn't even drunk that much, and he's already wasted.
If you make him drink any more,
he might die of shock.
Why be scared of something so silly?
Hey, kiddo!
If you are scared of dying,
go back to bed, coward!
Hey!
Who said that?!
How dare you slander your dear big brother like this?!
Let go.
Big brother this, big brother that.
You were born five seconds before me.
You think you're better than me, prick?!
You dare call me "prick"?!
I've argued with Dad for days on end.
Oh, wow!
- Hey, hey, hey, wait! - Whoa!
- Hey! - You want some?
You want this, Daeng?
Are you challenging me?!
I've never punched anyone in my twenty-five years of life.
Come! Bring it!
I saw that he opened his new coffee shop,
so we should support him.
- That's right, Auntie. - Since we're neighbors.
- We should be kind to each other. - Wow...
Oh!
So many customers.
[DO-MUN-DRIP]
Hello,
I'm Auntie Duang.
I own the restaurant upstairs.
This is Dawin.
He lives here, too.
Hello.
- Hello, hello. - Hello.
I brought you a gift for your grand opening.
Cool!
Is this the new Art Toy collection?
How cute.
No...
This is Nang Kwak.
Nang...Guac?
Nang Kwak, a wealth-beckoning goddess.
Nang Guac?
Nang Kwak.
Guac!
Kwak!
Guac.
"Kwak," as in...
Quick, quick, come here!
Business will be booming! Come, customers, come!
Oh!
"Kwak," like beckoning!
Yes, Nang Kwak!
Oh, I get it now.
Mm.
Take good care of her.
She can bring you luck.
Oh, then...
please tell them I can't wait to meet Lux.
I'll tell Lux that you said that.
- Hey! - Hey!
No, this is mine.
"Luck," like "May great fortune be with you."
Oh.
Then...
please thank Grace for me.
I'll tell her that.
- Hey! - Hey!
Never mind.
Just take good care of her.
Wherever she goes, business will be good.
Okay.
Do you really not know, or are you just messing with her?
I'm not messing with her.
I just came back from overseas.
I still can't remember...
some words.
- Mm... - Mm...
It's your first day, and you already have this many customers.
You're good at this, huh?
I'll order too, then.
One for me
and one for Dawin.
Of course, but...
you'll have to wait for a while.
I'm about to make...
my first customer's order.
- Huh?! - Huh?!
I've been waiting for an hour now.
When will we get ours, then?
You'll get them today.
You'll be my last order for today.
Today, I'll only sell ten cups.
- Huh?! - Huh?!
Ugh...when will I get my coffee?
Calm down, Auntie.
Good coffee
has to be ground slowly
to bring out its full flavor and aroma.
Why don't you get a grinder?
It's faster and more efficient.
I don't want speed.
What I want is the joy I get
from hearing the sound of coffee beans being slowly ground.
Slowly ground...
Crunch...crunch...
This is the joy of life.
Oh, do you feel the same way, Auntie?
It's not my idea,
but my husband's.
When he was chopping crispy pork belly,
he said exactly those words!
You are very lucky
to have such a cool husband.
What a role model.
Role model, my foot!
I don't want the coffee anymore.
It reminds me of my husband!
So irritating!
Give this back to me!
No more!
It'd be better if she stayed at my place!
Wait, Auntie Duang.
You haven't paid yet!
Ugh...I'm having bad luck again!
Bring me two cups.
I'll drink them myself.
Um...
Please wait a moment.
Three more orders to go.
Can I change my mind?
Just wait a little longer.
Really.
Is that so?
Yes.
One moment.
- Hey! - Calm down!
Ugh!
Stop. Let's get back to drinking, alright?
- Alright? - No!
Where did you learn to box?
I threw punch after punch,
and you dodged every damn one!
That's enough, Guard Dum.
Handyman Daeng, stop.
Let me get one clean punch in, then.
You dare fight back against your own brother?
No, no, no more.
- Stop fighting... - I'm older than you, you scoundrel!
You calling me a scoundrel
makes my blood boil, you bastard!
- You want some? Come here! - You want this, huh?!
Hey, stop!
Calm down!
That's enough.
Ugh, then you stop them!
I'm done. I'm tired, alright?!
Go ahead and deal with them!
Hey!
They're fighting,
and you're...
just going to let me stop them by myself?
What?
- Hey, what? - Hey...
- What? - See?!
You made Ms. Danis mad!
As your big brother,
I order you to apologize to her!
Big brother?
I don't like the sound of that.
I'll tell you this, then!
You're only older
because you were closer to Mom's coochie.
That's why you slipped out first!
I slipped out before you
because you were so big!
You had to squeeze through!
Like this!
- Hey, don't... - Well, if I came out before you,
you'd slip out...
like you were on the slides at Siam Amazing Park.
But I didn't do that, 'cause I love Mom very much.
I was clinging to Mom's ovaries like this.
When the doctor grabbed my leg,
I kicked him away!
Hey!
Can you two stop arguing about your mother's coochie?
- You... - Let's leave it at that for now.
But you and I!
- Come here! - Bring it!
Come on, then!
Hey...
- Bring it! - Why are you blocking me?!
You two... Hey!
- Ow... Hey, you! - Do it, then!
- Wait! Wait! - Bring it on!
Hey...
Hey, wait...
Wait...
Didn't you say you were allergic?
Who?
Someone like me
doesn't go down that easily!
- Oh, crap... - Oh, crap...
Mom.
I heard there's a new coffee shop.
How does it taste?
Don't know. I didn't have any.
Go ask Dawin instead.
He drank two cups.
He took quite a while.
Pretty nice.
Pretty strong.
Very strong!
Hey,
don't buy from him or hang around him.
I just don't like him.
Why, though?
What did he do to you?
He reminds me of your dad.
Huh?
He takes an hour to make a single drink.
He likes
the sound of the coffee beans cracking as he grinds them.
He sells ten cups of coffee a day.
He'll be rich real soon.
Hey, Mom,
you're judging him
just because he lives a slow life like Dad?
He didn't do anything wrong.
He was just doing what he enjoys.
He isn't causing trouble for anyone.
Really? Or have you never seen it before?
I saw Mom and Dad arguing about this all the time.
Suddenly, Dad disappeared.
He probably lives a slow life somewhere.
He left Mom and me to struggle.
And did you know
how your mother...
had to work hard
to provide for you while she was pregnant?
Did you see
Dad leave and just drift through life?
I know you're angry,
but don't try to make me hate Dad like you do, okay?
You can think whatever you want.
But our family
doesn't need him!
I'll take care of you and Mom.
Dawin,
can you read my fortune?
I want to know...
how much longer they'll keep fighting.
Forget your fortune.
Look at my eyes first...
They've been fighting all day.
Can I ask you something?
Mm.
Dolly wants to see his father,
but Dollar doesn't.
What about you?
Do you want to see him?
I don't know...
It isn't important anymore.
I think
the two people I want to wake up and see every morning
are the ones arguing behind us.
Dollar, Dolly, my boys,
you can fight, you can bicker,
you can do whatever you want.
I know that deep down,
you two love each other.
But having you two...
in my life...
is more than enough.
Ow...
- Boys. - Hey!
Boys...
Yes?
Let's hug, alright?
Okay, Mom.
Ow!
- Hey... - Ow, ow.
Dawin,
- let's read my fortune. - What? What?
- Dawin, read my... Ow! - What?!
- Boys? - What?!
At ease!
Sit!
Hug!
Hey!
There, hug your brother.
Hug!
Confess!
I'm sorry...
I... I love you very much.
I'm sorry, too.
Although you...
are such an optimist...
Ow!
Why did you say that?
Huh?!
Calm down.
Let me finish.
Although you...
are such an optimist,
without you,
my world would be much darker.
If you hadn't made that sacrifice for me,
I probably wouldn't have graduated either.
It's okay, Daeng.
Well...
I'm just dumb,
so there's no point in spending money
to send me to school anyway.
Aw...
How can you be this cute, Dum?
My dear Moo Deng...
I love you so much, my Bie Sukrit.
It's that simple!
There's no need to fight!
Wow!
You're amazing!
You can handle both Moo Deng
and Bie Sukrit!
Well done, tiger.
Hey, what tiger?
You said she was fierce like a dog just the other day.
Dax...
It's true.
Like a dog?!
Who?!
Don't listen to him.
He's drunk. Talking nonsense.
I'm not talking nonsense.
I still remember you saying,
"If you want a puppy,
you'll have to venture into a dog's den."
Hey, Dax!
Ow!
What?
Dog's den, huh?!
You said, "a dog's den", huh?
Not just any dog, either.
Temple dogs.
Hey... Dax!
Ow! When did I say that?
Temple dogs?!
Dax!
Shut your mouth! Ow!
Wait...no. Looks like she won't hit me.
Hey, sit back down!
If you're drunk, go back to sleep!
- I'm not... - You're not helping!
Everyone knows "Katy Perry."
But you're...
a burden I have to "carry."
Go back to sleep. Go!
Sit!
Sit down!
Quick!
Sleep!
You're not helping.
Hey, you don't have to listen to...
Ms. Danis?
Ms. Danis!
Wow...
She's fierce, just like Grandpa said!
[Open]
[Closed]
Yes, Father.
Dang!
It's a real Asian house gecko!
This is my first time seeing it.
It must be nice, huh?
Hungry? Just eat bugs.
Want to go somewhere? Just go.
Want to do something? Just do it.
You're free.
You don't have to worry about what other people think of you.
Hey, Mom.
Fighting all the time is actually kind of nice.
Dollar always takes us out for barbecue to cheer us up afterward!
Go ahead,
fight every day,
and I'll just disown you two.
It's annoying!
Ugh...don't be like that!
Hm?
Who's that, Mom?
Whoa!
What are you doing again, Dollar?!
- Ugh! - Hup!
You told me you wanted tires under your potted plants.
I found some, so I took them with me.
I can burn it off after a big meal, too.
Dolly,
- this is yours. - Huh?
- I brought it for you. - Ugh...
- Come on! - I knew it...
No wonder you're so fit.
You dragged two tires.
- Here! - Ow...
Ready! Go!
Go, go.
Put in some effort.
Mom...
Oh...
There.
He's the coffee shop owner I mentioned.
Oh, shit...
It pooped on my head.
Oh...
It stinks...
Gosh...
He's an oddball, isn't he?
Remember, sweethearts,
don't get involved with people like this.
What did Mom tell you?
Yeah...
Ms. Danis!
Oh, no...
She's drunk, too...
Ms. Danis!
Are there other ghosts here, too?
Whose voice is that?
Oh, no...
Grandpa?
You lied to me, Gramps.
Didn't you say you'd stay with me for a long time?
Why didn't you keep your promise, Gramps?
Didn't you teach me
not to promise anything
if I can't follow through?
Then why did you leave me?
I'm all alone now, Gramps.
Grandpa,
what did you tell her this time?
Like when you went and badmouthed me?
You do not know how hard her life was.
She was an orphan.
She worked to support herself from a young age.
The first time I met her
was when she rented a room here.
I saw how hard-working she was,
so I asked her to take care of the dorm and help take care of me, too.
She said that I
was like a relative to her.
When she was with me,
she was never lonely.
It was like she was finally living with her own family.
So, Grandpa,
you're saying all this...
because you want me to give some inheritance...
to your "favorite granddaughter," huh?
She was never interested in my inheritance.
Unlike my "bratty grandson!"
All you think about is selling my dorm!
Gramps...
Can I have one more hug, Gramps?
Please?
Please, Gramps.
I just want to hug you one more time,
okay?
I miss you, Gramps...
I miss you...
I miss you, too...
Gramps, I'm so lonely...
Gramps...
Please come back to me...
[The D Dorm]
Here.
You're hungover, right?
Soy milk,
you like to drink it when you're hungover.
How did you know I like to drink soy milk when I'm hungover?
Grandpa came to me in a dream
and told me you like to drink soy milk
when you're hungover....
That's not all, though.
There's more.
What did he say?
I am sorry
I broke my promise
to stay with you for a long time.
"I am sorry"
I broke my promise
to stay with you for a long time."
I may not be here anymore,
but I hope that...
you will be strong
and live a good life.
You are talented,
so even if I am not here anymore,
you will not be lonely,
because you...
have Dobby.
Although he...
might not be as great as me,
I believe
- he... - "He...
will stay by your side."
"He will keep you company."
"My good girl."
Gramps!
I graduated!
I even got first-class honors! Look!
Why are you excited, Danis?
I already know
you could do this,
my good girl.
Hey...
can you
ask Gramps to come into my dreams, too?
Huh?
Mm...
Well...I can't promise, though.
You remembered your dream so clearly.
It almost seemed like Gramps was telling you what to say.
Oh...
But...
he didn't just tell me about this.
Grandpa told me other things, too.
What is it?
Tell me.
Well...in my dream,
Grandpa seemed to...
have some regrets.
He wants to find his first love,
and...
one of her relatives
seems to live in one of these rooms.
So, he wanted you to help.
That's why
I went around knocking on doors.
And...
as you can see, it didn't work.
Oh...
So... you went around
knocking on doors a few days ago...
because of this?
Mm.
I shouldn't have spent money hosting that party...
Huh?
No, I...
What I mean is...
If that's what Gramps wants,
I'll gladly help.
I'll work with you.
Hey, let's do it Gen Z-style!
Fist bump.
You still want me to help, right?
Any generation works...
Okay.
- Work together... - That's enough.
- Too much force? - Mm.
You're going to help me?
Mm.
Ow, ow!
That hurts!
Ow!
You want some of this?!
Why do those two seem to hate each other so much?
It happened two years ago.
Want to hear it?
I've compiled a list of tenants
- from the North for you. - You're messing with me again.
Why does it have to be tenants from the North?
Well, back then,
Grandma Gaysorn and Grandpa
planned to run away to Chiang Mai,
so I thought it'd be best to start with the North.
This person...
♫The D Dorm, meet me at the D Dorm♫
♫Every step we take has a meaning♫
♫No path is ever meaningless♫
♫As long as our hearts keep searching♫
♫One day, we'll find what we're yearning for♫
♫Walking alone is fine, but it's better when you're by my side♫
♫It won't be lonely when you're here to walk beside♫
♫Like a love that waits, waits at the D Dorm♫
♫Like a love that remains, remains at the dorm♫
♫Meaningful love and good things await on every path♫
♫It might not be a coincidence that we get to meet♫
♫There might be hidden meanings on the path beneath our feet♫
♫Perhaps the D Dorm is what led me to meet you♫
[The D Dorm]